To get this point home,
let's go back to 2014.
I think it's very important [chuckles]
that you guys see this. All right.
Where's this post? 1st of April, 2014,
two likes.
This is where I started my personal
training journey, like I told you,
April 2014. Now, what you have here
is thousands of
repetitions of me making terrible posts,
completely misjudging my audience,
having no idea what I'm doing.
Here,
I'm taking a screenshot of my FitnessPal.
"Food logging may not work for everyone.
I find that it's an effective way of
measuring my mac..." Well done, James.
Great post, bro. Fantastic.
I am the guy that you
would want to take the piss out of.
There's food prep here.
Like someone's going to see me putting
fucking veggies and chicken in Tupperware
and thinking, "Wow,
how the hell do I follow you?"
But the thing is, I even post
memes. Should I work out today? Yes,
go work
out. No. Yes, you should.
But at least when I did this, every single
post that I made gave me feedback.
It gave me an
idea of whether or not someone
was interested.
I would tell people how many teaspoons of
sugar are in a fucking
orange juice or whatever it is,
explaining what fat grips are.
I think I was using these in a workout,
so I was like, do you know what?
I'll just post about it. Four likes.
If I saw something in the newspaper,
I'd just take a picture, do a little post.
And again, these are the things,
the repetitions, that none of you ever
saw